<resources>
    <string name="app_name">5 Things</string>


    <string name="back_button">Link on kinopoisk</string>
    <string name="email_button">Send  to the author </string>
    <string name="check_account">Must see!</string>
    <string name="text_header">ВAnnex "5 things", I propose five films which in my opinion
     should definitely look at. Click on the poster =)</string>
    <string name="chooser_title">Select your browser</string>
    <string name="limitlessInfo">
       Limitless is a 2011 American thriller film directed by Neil Burger.
        Based on the novel The Dark Fields by Alan Glynn,
        the film stars Bradley Cooper, Abbie Cornish, and Robert De Niro.
        The events portrayed in the film follow Edward Morra, a struggling writer,
        who is introduced to a nootropic drug called NZT-48,
        which gives him the ability to fully utilize his brain and vastly improve his lifestyle.
    </string>
    <string name="lock">
       Lock, Stock and Two Smoking Barrels is a 1998 British crime comedy film written and directed by Guy Ritchie.
        The story is a heist film involving a self-confident young card sharp
        who loses £500,000 to a powerful crime lord in a rigged game of three card brag.
        To pay off his debts, he and his friends decide to rob a small-time gang
        who happen to be operating out of the flat next door.
        The film brought Guy Ritchie international acclaim and introduced actors Vinnie Jones,
        a former Wales international footballer, and Jason Statham, a former diver, to worldwide audiences.
        Based on a $1.35 million budget, the film had a box office gross of $28.3 million,
        making it a commercial success.
    </string>
    <string name="yes_man">Yes Man is a 2008 British–American comedy film directed by Peyton Reed,
        written by Nicholas Stoller, Jarrad Paul, and Andrew Mogel
        and starring Jim Carrey and co-starring Zooey Deschanel.
        The film is based loosely on the 2005 book Yes Man by British humorist Danny Wallace,
        who also makes a cameo appearance in the film.
  </string>
    <string name="thedep">
   The Departed is a 2006 American crime drama film, directed by Martin Scorsese and written by William Monahan.
        It is a remake of the 2002 Hong Kong film Infernal Affairs.
        The film stars Leonardo DiCaprio, Matt Damon, Jack Nicholson, and Mark Wahlberg,
        with Martin Sheen, Ray Winstone, Vera Farmiga, Anthony Anderson, and Alec Baldwin in supporting roles.</string>
    <string name="recolver">
        Revolver is a 2005 crime thriller film co-written and directed by Guy Ritchie and starring Jason Statham,
        Ray Liotta, Vincent Pastore and André Benjamin.
        The film centres on a revenge-seeking confidence trickster whose weapon is a universal formula
        that guarantees victory to its user, when applied to any game or confidence trick.</string>
    <string name="lim">http://www.kinopoisk.ru/film/462606/</string>
    <string name="lock_link">http://www.kinopoisk.ru/film/522/</string>
    <string name="yes">http://www.kinopoisk.ru/film/391772/</string>
    <string name="depe">http://www.kinopoisk.ru/film/81314/</string>
    <string name="revolve">http://www.kinopoisk.ru/film/18973/</string>
    <string name="not_client"> There are no email clients installed.</string>
    <string name="send_email"> Send email </string>
    <string name="subject_email"> subject of email </string>
</resources>
